<resources>
    <string name="app_name" formatted="false">BookStore</string>
    <string name="preference_file" formatted="false">com.example.bookstore.preference_books</string>
    <string name="bio_amitav_ghosh" formatted="false">Amitav Ghosh (born 11 July 1956)
        is an Indian writer. He won the 54th Jnanpith award in 2018
        , India\'s highest literary honor. Ghosh\'s ambitious novels use
        complex narrative strategies to probe the nature of national and personal
        identity, particularly of the people of India and South Asia.
        He has written historical fiction and also written non-fiction works
        discussing topics such as colonialism and climate change.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_amitav_ghosh" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/c/c0/Amitav_Ghosh_by_Gage_Skidmore.jpg/220px-Amitav_Ghosh_by_Gage_Skidmore.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_sea_of_poppies" formatted="false">The novel interweaves the stories of a number of characters, who all, in the latter half of the novel, find themselves taking passage from Calcutta to Mauritius on a schooner named the Ibis.  The story begins with Deeti, a simple, pious lady, caring mother and an efficient housewife. Married to Hukam Singh, a crippled worker in the Ghazipur Opium Factory, the unfortunate Deeti figures out that on her wedding night, she was drugged with opium by her mother-in-law, so that her brother-in-law could rape her and consummate the marriage in place of her impotent husband. This brother-in-law is the real father of Deeti\'s daughter Kabutri. When her husband dies, Deeti sends Kabutri to stay with relatives. Deeti looks almost certain to meet her doom when she is forced to consider sati ritual (immolation on her husband\'s funeral pyre) as the only option in the face of threats of more rapes by the brother-in-law, but then Kalua, the untouchable caste ox man from the neighbouring village, comes to her rescue. The couple flee and unite. This is not acceptable to the high caste villagers. In order to escape Deeti\'s in-laws, she and Kalua become indentured servants, travelling on the Ibis.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_sea_of_poppies" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/3/37/Ghosh_amitav_Sea_of_Poppies.jpg/220px-Ghosh_amitav_Sea_of_Poppies.jpg</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_the_hungry_tide" formatted="false">https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/File:The_Hungry_Tide.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_the_hungry_tide" formatted="false">Off the easternmost coast of India, in the Bay of Bengal, lies the immense labyrinth of tiny islands known as the Sundarbans. For settlers here, life is precarious: attacks by deadly tigers are common, and the threat of eviction and consequent social unrest is ever present. Without warning, at any time, tidal floods rise and surge over the land, leaving devastation in their wake. In this place of vengeful beauty, the lives of three people from different worlds collide.  The main character, Piyali Roy, is a young marine biologist of Bengali-Indian descent but identifying as stubbornly American. Raised in Seattle, she studies at the Scripps Institute of Oceanography in La Jolla. She travels to the Sundarbans in search of a rare endangered river dolphin, Orcaella brevirostris. She meets Kanai Dutt, a translator and businessman, on the Kolkata Suburban Railway heading towards Port Canning, on her way to the Sundarbans. Upon her arrival, she hires a boat to look for the dolphins, but her journey begins with a disaster, when she is thrown from a boat into crocodile-infested waters. Rescue comes in the form of an illiterate young fisherman, Fokir. Although they have no language between them, Piya and Fokir are powerfully drawn to each other, sharing an uncanny instinct for the ways of the sea. Piya engages Fokir to help with her research and finds a translator in Kanai, whose idealistic aunt and uncle are longtime settlers in the Sundarbans. As the three of them explore the tidal backwaters, they are drawn unaware into the hidden undercurrents of this isolated world, where political turmoil exacts a personal toll that is every bit as powerful as the ravaging tide.  The Morichjhanpi massacre of 1978–79, when the government of West Bengal forcibly evicted thousands of Bengali refugees who had settled on the island, forms a background for some parts of the novel. The novel explores topics such as humanism and environmentalism, especially when they come into conflict.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_the_shadow_lines" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/a/a4/The_Shadow-lines.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_the_shadow_lines" formatted="false">Split into two parts (\'Going Away\' and \'Coming Home\'), the novel follows the life of a young boy growing up in Calcutta, who is educated in Delhi and then follows with the experiences he has in London.  His family – the Datta Chaudhuris - and the Price family in London are linked by the friendship between their respective patriarchs – Justice Datta Chaudhuri and Lionel Tresawsen. The narrator adores Tridib, his uncle, because of his tremendous knowledge and his perspective of the incidents and places. Tha\'mma thinks that Tridib is the type of person who seems \'determined to waste his life in idle self-indulgence\', one who refuses to use his family connections to establish a career. Unlike his grandmother, the narrator loves listening to Tridib.  For the narrator, Tridib\'s lore is very different from the collection of facts and figures. The narrator is sexually attracted to Ila but his feelings are passive. He never expresses his feelings to her afraid to lose the relationship that exists between them. However, one day he involuntarily shows his feelings when she, unaware of his feelings for her, undresses in front of him. She feels sorry for him but immediately abandons him to visit Nick\'s (the Price family\'s son, and the man who she later marries) bedroom. Tha\'mma does not like Ila; she continually asks the narrator \"Why do you always speak for that whore?\" Tha\'mma has a dreadful past and wants to reunite her family and goes to Dhaka to bring back her uncle. Tridib is in love with May and sacrificed his life to rescue her from mobs in the communal riots of 1963–64 in Dhaka.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_river_of_smoke" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/9/9f/River_of_smoke.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_river_of_smoke" formatted="false">The promotional text refers to the storyline which can be summarized as follows: After the incidents on Ibis, which was caught in a storm and eventually ended up in Mauritius, but with a few passengers less, the story help in this novel begins from where it left off. From the details of the changing lives and traditions of Indian migrants in Mauritius, the novel traces the fate of other characters from Ibis and describes the opium trade in China. The novel has a rich tapestry of characters from various cultural and geographical backgrounds whose common interest is trade with China. The plot is set in Fanqui town, a small strip of land used by foreigners to trade with local Chinese traders, a year before the first opium war.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_the_great_derangement" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/3/3a/The_Great_Derangement.jpg/220px-The_Great_Derangement.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_the_great_derangement" formatted="false">The book is composed of three parts: Part I, titled Stories, Part II, History, and Part III, Politics. The first part, Stories, explores why the modern novel struggles as an art form to describe and grapple with the concept of climate change. To understand this shortcoming, Ghosh highlights the role of the uncanny. In the second section, History, Ghosh highlights the role of colonialism in the climate crisis. With examples ranging from Miami to Mumbai to New York, Ghosh explores why urban planning deviated and deviates from the indigenous multigenerational knowledge that compelled cultures to build away from the ocean. In the final section, Politics, Ghosh notes that activists who single out capitalism as the systemic driver of climate change miss an important element: imperialism. Ghosh describes how writers and artists increased their engagement with political movements at the same time as industrial activities intensified. Ghosh ties these three sections together with a comparison between the Paris Agreement and Pope Francis\'s 2015 encyclical on climate change.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_the_glass_palace" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/f/fb/The_Glass_Palace.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_the_glass_palace" formatted="false">The novel starts with an 11-year-old boy called Rajkumar running through the city of Mandalay to find a woman called Ma Cho. He is the last surviving member of his family and comes to Burma from India with a bright entrepreneurial spirit and a hunger for success.  Rajkumar\'s work as an assistant on Ma Cho\'s food stall takes place in the shadow of the Glass Palace, in which King Thibaw and his wife reside with their daughters, the princesses. As the Third Anglo-Burmese War breaks out, everyday citizens of Mandalay are able to enter the enshrined building, and it is then that Rajkumar spots Dolly, one of the princesses\' attendants, and instantly falls in love with her. However, the entire Royal Family and their entourage are quickly extradited by the British and sent into house arrest thousands of miles away on the West coast of India.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_gun_island" formatted="false">https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81h+GfNqXxL._SY342_.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_gun_island" formatted="false">Bundook. Gun. A common word, but one which turns Deen Datta\'s world upside down. A dealer of rare books, Deen is used to a quiet life spent indoors, but as his once-solid beliefs begin to shift, he is forced to set out on an extraordinary journey; one that takes him from India to Los Angeles and Venice via a tangled route through the memories and experiences of those he meets along the way. There is Piya, a fellow Bengali-American who sets his journey in motion; Tipu, an entrepreneurial young man who opens Deen\'s eyes to the realities of growing up in today\'s world; Rafi, with his desperate attempt to help someone in need; and Cinta, an old friend who provides the missing link in the story they are all a part of. It is a journey which will upend everything he thought he knew about himself, about the Bengali legends of his childhood and about the world around him. Gun Island is a beautifully realised novel which effortlessly spans space and time. It is the story of a world on the brink, of increasing displacement and unstoppable transition. But it is also a story of hope, of a man whose faith in the world and the future is restored by two remarkable women.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_the_nutmeg_curse" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/e/ea/The_Nutmeg%27s_Curse.jpg/220px-The_Nutmeg%27s_Curse.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_the_nutmeg_curse" formatted="false">Before the 18th century, every single nutmeg in the world originated around a group of small volcanic islands east of Java, known as the Banda Islands. As the nutmeg made its way across the known world, they became immensely valuable - in 16th century Europe, just a handful could buy a house. It was not long before European traders became conquerors, and the indigenous Bandanese communities - and the islands themselves - would pay a high price for access to this precious commodity. Yet the bloody fate of the Banda Islands forewarns of a threat to our present day. Amitav Ghosh argues that the nutmeg\'s violent trajectory from its native islands is revealing of a wider colonial mindset which justifies the exploitation of human life and the natural environment, and which dominates geopolitics to this day. Written against the backdrop of the pandemic and the Black Lives Matter protests, and interweaving discussions on everything from climate change, the migrant crisis, and the animist spirituality of indigenous communities around the world, The Nutmeg\'s Curse offers a sharp critique of Western society, and reveals the profoundly remarkable ways in which human history is shaped by non-human forces.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_the_calcutta_chromosome" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/5/59/The_Calcutta_Chromosome.jpg/220px-The_Calcutta_Chromosome.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_the_calcutta_chromosome" formatted="false">The novel begins with the story of Antar, a resident of the future New York doing data processing for the International Water Council. A chance bit of data causes Antar to recall a bizarre encounter he had with L. Murugan, an employee of the LifeWatch organization (Antar\'s former employer), who disappeared in Calcutta in 1995. Murugan had asked to be transferred to Calcutta because of his fascination with the life of Sir Ronald Ross. While Antar tries to track Murugan’s movements in Calcutta through the digitized archives, another narrative thread follows Murugan directly as his path brings him into contact with a variety of other characters, some more savory than others. The plot is quite complex and its timelines are deliberately mixed up, switching from Antar\'s time to Murugan\'s to Ross\'s and back over the course of as many chapters.  Through his research into old and lost documents and phone messages, Antar determines that Murugan had systematically unearthed a deep secret lurking behind Ross\'s malaria research — an underground scientific and mystical movement that could grant eternal life. Loosely described, the process of securing this form of immortality is as follows: the disciples of this movement can transfer their chromosomes into another\'s body, and gradually become that person or take over that person. In the novel, Ronald Ross did not discover the mysteries of the malaria parasite; it was a group of underground practitioners of a different, mystical \"science,\" natives of India, who helped to guide Ross to the conclusions for which he is famous. These native Indians provided Ross with clues in the belief that in the moment Ross made his discovery, the parasite would change its nature. At this point, a new variant of malaria would emerge and the group\'s research using the chromosome-transfer technique would advance even further.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_flood_of_fire" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/d/df/Flood_of_Fire_book_cover.jpg/220px-Flood_of_Fire_book_cover.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_flood_of_fire" formatted="false">Following the storylines of the previous two parts, Sea of Poppies and River of Smoke, the story continues in 1839. Kesri Singh, brother of Deeti, is made aware that Deeti ran away from her husband\'s pyre by avoiding sati. She eloped with a lower-caste labourer and Singh\'s family is ashamed of the events. Kesri joins the British service as an Indian soldier at the rank of sepoy. He works for the East India Company, where his superior is Deeti\'s deceased husband\'s brother. Zachary Reid, an American soldier born to a quadroon mother and a white father, pretends to be white and starts entering the trading business. Shireen Modi, an Indian Parsi woman, has left for China in search of her late husband\'s illegitimate child. In her pursuit, she starts to have feelings for her husband\'s close friend who is now helping her. She is fully aware that her relationship with this Armenian friend would be condemned by her orthodox Parsi community. Neel Rattan Halder, once a king, has been separated from his son after he was arrested by the British. Neel has now absconded and remains a fugitive in order to avoid being jailed for his conviction on the false forgery charges, which Mr. Burnham had manipulated. The First Opium War has commenced and the characters find themselves in midst of these events.</string>
    <string name="bio_salman_rushdie" formatted="false">Ahmed Salman Rushdie was born in Bombay on 19 June 1947 during the British Raj, into an Indian Kashmiri Muslim family. He is the son of Anis Ahmed Rushdie, a Cambridge-educated lawyer-turned-businessman, and Negin Bhatt, a teacher. Rushdie\'s father was dismissed from the Indian Civil Services (ICS) after it emerged that the birth certificate submitted by him had changes to make him appear younger than he was. Rushdie has three sisters. He wrote in his 2012 memoir that his father adopted the name Rushdie in honour of Averroes (Ibn Rushd).  Rushdie grew up in Bombay and was educated at the Cathedral and John Connon School in Fort, South Bombay, before moving to England in 1954 to attend Rugby School in Rugby, Warwickshire, and then King\'s College, Cambridge, from which he graduated with a Bachelor of Arts degree in history.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_salman_rushdie" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/commons/thumb/9/92/Salman_Rushdie_2014_%28cropped%29.jpg/220px-Salman_Rushdie_2014_%28cropped%29.jpg</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_the_satanic_verse" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/c/c8/1988_Salman_Rushdie_The_Satanic_Verses.jpg/220px-1988_Salman_Rushdie_The_Satanic_Verses.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_the_satanic_verse" formatted="false">The Satanic Verses consists of a frame narrative, using elements of magical realism, interlaced with a series of sub-plots that are narrated as dream visions experienced by one of the protagonists. The frame narrative, like many other stories by Rushdie, involves Indian expatriates in contemporary England. The two protagonists, Gibreel Farishta and Saladin Chamcha, are both actors of Indian Muslim background. Farishta is a Bollywood superstar who specialises in playing Hindu deities (the character is partly based on Indian film stars Amitabh Bachchan and N. T. Rama Rao). Chamcha is an emigrant who has broken with his Indian identity and works as a voiceover artist in England.  At the beginning of the novel, both are trapped in a plane hijacked by Sikh separatists, flying from India to Britain. The plane explodes over the English Channel, but the two are magically saved. In a miraculous transformation, Farishta takes on the personality of the archangel Gabriel and Chamcha that of a devil. Chamcha is arrested and passes through an ordeal of police abuse as a suspected illegal immigrant.</string>
    <string name="synopsis_midnight_children" formatted="false">Midnight\'s Children is a loose allegory for events in 1947 British Raj India and after the partition of India. The protagonist and narrator of the story is Saleem Sinai, born at the exact moment when India became an independent country. He was born with telepathic powers, as well as an enormous and constantly dripping nose with an extremely sensitive sense of smell. The novel is divided into three books.  The first book begins with the story of the Sinai family, particularly with events leading up to the fall of British Colonial India and the partition. Saleem is born precisely at midnight, 15 August 1947, therefore, exactly as old as independent India. He later discovers that all children born in India between 12 a.m. and 1 a.m. on that date are imbued with special powers. Saleem, using his telepathic powers, assembles a Midnight Children\'s Conference, reflective of the issues India faced in its early statehood concerning the cultural, linguistic, religious, and political differences faced by a vastly diverse nation. Saleem acts as a telepathic conduit, bringing hundreds of geographically disparate children into contact while also attempting to discover the meaning of their gifts. In particular, those children born closest to the stroke of midnight wield more powerful gifts than the others. Shiva \"of the Knees\", Saleem\'s nemesis, and Parvati, called \"Parvati-the-witch,\" are two of these children with notable gifts and roles in Saleem\'s story.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_midnight_children" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/9/9d/MidnightsChildren.jpg/220px-MidnightsChildren.jpg</string>

    <string name="synopsis_victory_city" formatted="false">Victory City is framed as a fictional translation of an epic originally written in Sanskrit. The narrator and protagonist is Pampa Kampana, partly inspired by the historical, fourteenth-century princess-poet Gangadevi, who is given (or cursed with) a 247-year lifespan. Through her magical powers, she wills into existence the empire Bisnaga, and its capital city of the same name, inspired largely by the historical fourteenth- to sixteenth-century Empire of Vijayanagara, and rules it as what one review calls \"a sort of feminist utopia\", variously as a minister, regent, and queen consort, for over two hundred years. Covering multiple generations, her reign includes having affairs with Portuguese adventurers and turning people into animals with her spells. Eventually, Bisnaga is brought down by political intrigue, competing neighbours, and religious bigotry.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_victory_city" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/4/4b/Victory_City_book_cover.png/220px-Victory_City_book_cover.png</string>
    <string name="synopsis_shame" formatted="false">Shame is Salman Rushdie\'s third novel, published in 1983. This book was written out of a desire to approach the problem of \"artificial\" (other-made) country divisions, their residents\' complicity, and the problems of post-colonialism when Pakistan was created to separate the Muslims from the Hindus after Britain gave up control of India.  The book is written in the style of magic realism. It portrays the lives of Iskander Harappa (sometimes assumed to be Zulfikar Ali Bhutto), and General Raza Hyder (sometimes assumed to be General Muhammad Zia-ul-Haq), and their relationship. The central theme of the novel is that begetting \"shame\" begets violence. The concepts of \'shame\' and \'shamelessness\' are explored through all of the characters, with the main focus being on Sufiya Zinobia and Omar Khayyám.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_shame" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/e/e0/ShameNovel.JPG/220px-ShameNovel.JPG</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_haroun" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/a/a0/Haroun_and_the_Sea_of_Stories_%28book_cover%29.jpg/220px-Haroun_and_the_Sea_of_Stories_%28book_cover%29.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_haroun" formatted="false">At the beginning of the story, protagonist Haroun Khalifa lives with his father Rashid, a famous storyteller and doctor, and his mother Soraya, until the latter is seduced by their neighbour \"Mr. Sengupta\" to leave home. Thereafter, Rashid is hired to speak on behalf of local politicians but fails his initial assignment. With Haroun in tow, Rashid is thence conveyed to the \"Valley of K\" by courier \"Mr. Butt,\" to speak for \"Snooty Buttoo,\" another politician. Attempting to sleep aboard Buttoo\'s yacht, Haroun discovers \"Iff the Water Genie,\" assigned to detach Rashid\'s imagination, and demands to speak with Iff\'s supervisor, the Walrus, to argue against this decision. They are then carried to the eponymous \"Sea of Stories\" by an artificial intelligence in the form of a hoopoe, nicknamed \"Butt\" after the courier. In the Sea of Stories, Haroun learns the Sea is endangered by antagonist \"Khattam-Shud,\" who represents the end.</string>
    <string name="synopsis_enchantress_of_florence" formatted="false">The central theme of The Enchantress of Florence is the visit of a European to the Mughal emperor Akbar\'s court and his claim that he is a long lost relative of Akbar, born of an exiled Indian princess and an Italian from Florence. The story moves between continents, the court of Akbar to Renaissance Florence mixing history, fantasy and fable.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_the_enchantress_of_florence" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/b/bd/Enchantress_of_florence.jpg/220px-Enchantress_of_florence.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_quichotte" formatted="false">The protagonist, Sam DuChamp, is an Indian-born writer living in America and author of a number of unsuccessful spy thrillers. Hoping to write a book \"radically unlike any other he had ever attempted\", he creates the character of Ismail Smile. Smile, who was born in Bombay, is a travelling pharmaceutical salesman who has suffered a stroke in old age. He begins obsessively watching reality television and becomes infatuated with Salma R, a former Bollywood star who hosts a daytime talk show in New York City. Despite having never met her, he sends her love letters under the pen name \"Quichotte\". He begins a quest for her across America, driving in his Chevrolet Cruze with his imaginary son Sancho. The two experience contemporary issues of the United States, including racism, the opioid epidemic, familial love, and the impact of popular culture. The lives of the character Quichotte and the writer DuChamp intertwine as the story progresses.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_quichotte" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/7/7d/Quichotte_%28Rushdie_novel%29.png/220px-Quichotte_%28Rushdie_novel%29.png</string>
    <string name="synopsis_imaginary_homelands" formatted="false">Salman Rushdie\'s Imaginary Homelands is an important record of one writer’s intellectual and personal odyssey. The seventy essays collected here, written over the last ten years, cover an astonishing range of subjects –the literature of the received masters and of Rushdie’s contemporaries; the politics of colonialism and the ironies of culture; film, politicians, the Labour Party, religious fundamentalism in America, racial prejudice; and the preciousness of the imagination and of free expression. For this paperback edition, the author has written a new essay to mark the third anniversary of the fatwa.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_imaginary_homelands" formatted="false">https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91CSes3DChL._SY342_.jpg</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_luka_and_fire_of_life" formatted="false">https://upload.wikimedia.org/wikipedia/en/thumb/6/6d/Luka_and_the_Fire_of_Life.jpg/220px-Luka_and_the_Fire_of_Life.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_luka_and_fire_of_life" formatted="false">The book opens with protagonist Luka and his father Rashid walking home from Luka\'s school in the fictional city of Kahani in the land of Alifbay. They pass the Great Rings of Fire circus, where, upon seeing the pitiful state of the animals, Luka yells: \"May your animals stop obeying your commands and your rings of fire eat up your stupid tent\". (Rushdie 6) Later that day, the animals revolt and the rings of fire consume the tents; and Dog and Bear (a bear and a dog respectively), two animals from the circus, become Luka\'s faithful pets. (Rushdie 4) One month afterward, Rashid enters a coma, attributed to a curse placed by antagonist \'Captain Aag\'. Thereafter, Luka travels through the \'World of Magic\' imagined by his father, guided by a phantom-like creature nicknamed \'Nobodaddy\', representing Rashid\'s imminent death. Bear is identified as Barak of the it-Barak (a set of immortal dog-men), turned into a dog by a Chinese curse; and Dog as the monarch of a northern land, transformed by an ogre. All four seek the eponymous \'Fire of Life\' to revive Rashid. At the River of Time, which they must follow to find the Fire, they are attacked by the Old Man of the River, who kills Luka. Once revived, Luka realizes that this world will revive him continually until he achieves his purpose, or exceeds his chances of doing so. Luka eventually bests the Old Man in a game of riddles. The protagonists then find a boat but are soon capsized and thereafter carried upriver by the Elephant Ducks: \"a pair of absurd creatures with duck-like bodies and large elephant heads\" (Rushdie 66).</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_fightOfCentury" formatted="false">https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71CSwrXfruL._SY342_.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_fightOfCentury" formatted="false">"To mark its 100-year anniversary, the American Civil Liberties Union partners with award-winning authors Michael Chabon and Ayelet Waldman to bring together many of our greatest living writers, each contributing an original piece inspired by a historic ACLU case. "</string>
    <string name="bio_mary_kubica" formatted="false">Mary Kubica is a New York Times bestselling author of thrillers including The Good Girl, The Other Mrs., Local Woman Missing and Just the Nicest Couple. Her books have been translated into over thirty languages and have sold over two million copies worldwide. Her novels have been praised as \"hypnotic\" (People) and \"thrilling and illuminating\" (L.A. Times). She lives outside of Chicago with her husband and children.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_mary_kubica" formatted="false">https://encrypted-tbn1.gstatic.com/images?q=tbn:ANd9GcQ4Op3xVlb4qgX3ihrV-LUJZHPhb1v6HR8ZH6sqwDyQh0FTI_Dw</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_local_woman_missing" formatted="false">https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81v4RTUBB5L._SY342_.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_local_woman_missing" formatted="false">In this smart and chilling thriller, master of suspense Mary Kubica takes domestic secrets to a whole new level, showing that some people will stop at nothing to keep the truth buried.  People don\'t just disappear without a trace…  Shelby Tebow is the first to go missing. Not long after, Meredith Dickey and her six-year-old daughter, Delilah, vanish just blocks away from where Shelby was last seen, striking fear into their once-peaceful community. Are these incidents connected? After an elusive search that yields more questions than answers, the case eventually goes cold.  Now, eleven years later, Delilah shockingly returns. Everyone wants to know what happened to her, but no one is prepared for what they\'ll find…</string>
    <string name="synopsis_the_good_girl" formatted="false">tory of a rich girls kidnapping due to her Daddys injustices. Mia(Chloe) was kidnapped by Colin (Owen) but instead of following the kidnapping plan Owen took her to an empty cabin in the woods. Chloe ends up falling in love with Owen over the length of time they spent in the cabin.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_the_good_girl" formatted="false">https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81Wiq3QpLJL._SY342_.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_just_nicest_couple" formatted="false">Lily Scott, Nina\'s friend and coworker, thinks she may have been the last to see Jake before he went missing. After Lily confesses everything to her husband, Christian, the two decide that nobody can find out what happened leading up to Jake\'s disappearance, especially not Nina.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_just_nicest_couple" formatted="false">https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/412klW5nn8L._SY445_SX342_.jpg</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_the_other_mrs" formatted="false">https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/71ujjeKUiML._SY342_.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_the_other_mrs" formatted="false">Kubica tells the story of Sadie Foust and her family, who have relocated from urban Chicago to rural Maine, only to be shocked by the violent murder of a neighbor.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_pretty_baby" formatted="false">https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/A1rcJ8T9TcL._SY342_.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_pretty_baby" formatted="false">Heidi Wood has always been a charitable woman: she works for a nonprofit, takes in stray cats. Still, her husband and daughter are horrified when Heidi returns home one day with a young woman named Willow and her four-month-old baby in tow. Disheveled and apparently homeless, this girl could be a criminal—or worse.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_dont_you_cry" formatted="false">https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91SswDHcUXL._SY342_.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_dont_you_cry" formatted="false">In downtown Chicago, a young woman named Esther Vaughan disappears from her apartment without a trace. A haunting letter addressed to My Dearest is found among her possessions, leaving her friend and roommate Quinn Collins to wonder where Esther is and whether or not she\'s the person Quinn thought she knew.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_every_last_lie" formatted="false">https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/81GAC1W+RPL._SY342_.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_every_last_lie" formatted="false">Legal investigator Finley O\'Sullivan searches for evidence the police overlooked, wading through secrets, lies, and betrayal to find answers. With the unsolved murder of her husband still very much on her mind, Finley must confront her own personal trauma on a daily basis.</string>
    <string name="imageUrl_when_lights_go_out" formatted="false">https://m.media-amazon.com/images/I/91NgimaD7WL._SY342_.jpg</string>
    <string name="synopsis_when_lights_go_out" formatted="false">Kubica presents the story of Jessie Sloane, a young twenty year old, who faces the heaviness of her mother\'s last days after a diagnosis of cancer. Jessica fights sleep with a troublesome case of insomnia. In a zombie-like state, she keeps watchful vigil over her mother.</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" formatted="false">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>